var Store = {
  questions: [
    //1
    {
      question: "How old is the art of barbecue?",
      options: [
        "a. Invented in the 1950's",
        "b. Invented by Abraham Lincoln in 1830",
        "c. Has been around ever since meat was cooked over an open flame",
        "d. Since Roman times",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    //2
    {
      question: "What are the major barbecue styles of the United States?",
      options: [
        "a. North, South, East, West",
        "b. Maine style and Oregon Style",
        "c. New York, Deep Dish, and Detroit",
        "d. Texas, Carolina, Kansas City and Alabama",
      ],
      answer: 3,
    },
    //3
    {
      question: "Which style is know for using beef as the main meat source?",
      options: [
        "a.Carolina",
        "b.Alabama",
        "c.Texas",
        "d. Kansas City"],
      answer: 2,
    },
    //4
    {
      question: "Which region is famous for having 3 different styles of barbecue?",
      options: [
        "a.Alabama",
        "b.Carolina",
        "c.Texas",
        "d.Kansas City"
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    //5
    {
      question: "Which region is considered the crossroads of bbq?",
      options: [
        "a. Texas",
        "b. Alabama",
        "c. Kansas City",
        "d. Florida"],
      answer: 2,
    },
    //6
    {
      question: "Which region is famous for having white barbecue sauce?",
      options: [
        "a. Alabama",
        "b. Delaware",
        "c. Pacific Northwest",
        "d. Homestyle",
      ],
      answer: 0,
    },
    //7
    {
      question: "How is barbecue typically cooked?",
      options: [
        "a. Hot and Fast",
        "b. COld and Quick",
        "c. Microwave",
        "d. Low and Slow",
      ],
      answer: 3,
    },
    //8
    {
      question: "What temperature is most barbecue cooked to?",
      options: [
        "a. 145째F",
        "b. 32째F",
        "c. 203째C",
        "d. 203째F"],
      answer: 3,
    },
    //9
    {
      question: "What type of heat is used for cooking barbecue?",
      options: [
        "a. Searing",
        "b. Indirect heat",
        "c. Sous vide",
        "d. Flash fry",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    //10
    {
      question: "WHich tool is most important for cooking barbecue?",
      options: [
        "a.Kitchen sink",
        "b. Grill/smoker",
        "c. Knife",
        "d. Spatula"],
      answer: 1,
    },
  ],
  correctAnswers: 0,
  questionIndex: 0,
  quizStarted: false
};
